Register of the Oshkosh (Winnebago County, Wis.: Town). Clerk: Clerk's Records, 1841-1966
Wisconsin Historical Society
Oshkosh (Winnebago County, Wis.: Town). Clerk: Clerk's Records, 1841-1966
Oshkosh (Winnebago County, Wis.: Town). Clerk
Winnebago Series 65
3.2 c.f. (9 archives boxes)
Housed at the Archives Area Research Center, Polk Library, University of Wisconsin Oshkosh; owned by the Wisconsin Historical Society, Library-Archives Division
Reports and papers of the town clerk including minutes of town meetings, financial records, election records, school statistics, highway commission papers, and other records filed with the clerk.
Contents List
- General Records
  - 1868-1902 (Box 1, Folder 1-3)
  - 1903-1934 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - 1934-1955 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 1956-1966 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Agreements, Contracts and Miscellaneous Business Records, 1853-1911 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Agricultural Statistics, 1874-1904 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Assessor's Certified Report of Railroads, 1900, 1906 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Assessor's Fieldbook, 1930-1932 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Assessor's Preliminary Statement of Real Estate, 1903-1904 (Box 5, Folder 1-3)
- Board of Health Reports, 1879-1881, 1932-1933, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Chattel Mortgages, 1877-1914 (Box 5, Folder 5-9)
- Draft and Enlistment Records, 1864, 1868 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Election Records
  - General, 1867-1881 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Town, 1868-1905 (Box 6, Folder 1-2)
  - Campaign Expense Statements, 1916-1925, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Late Registration Forms, 1868-1869 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Official Oaths, 1869-1882 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Poll Lists, 1876-1881, 1918-1924 (Box 6, Folder 6-7)
  - Registers of Voters, 1865-1868 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Statement of Votes, 1869-1922 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Tally Sheets, 1869-1930 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Financial Records
  - Proceedings of the Town Board, 1928-1935 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Report of the Town of Oshkosh, 1937-1958 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Report of the Town Supervisors, 1870-1898 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Report of the Town Treasurer, 1871-1916 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Winnebago County Farm Bureau, 1921-1924 (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Highways and Roads
  - Highway Records, 1868-1899 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
  - Road Records, 1849-1863 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Decisions, Orders and Resolutions of Supervisors, 1846-1916 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Minutes of Commissioners' Meeting, 1845 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Notices of Meetings of Supervisors, 1844-1921 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Petitions to the Supervisors, 1841-1905, 1947 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Property Damage Compensation, 1882-1905 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Releases, 1886-1908 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Surveys, 1844-1851 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Indentures, 1851, 1876 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Lease with the Ku Klux Klan, 1926 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Legal Records - Miscellaneous Lawsuits, 1852-1874 (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Liquor
  - Applications for Liquor Licenses, 1891-1916 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - License Revocation Suit, 1910 (Box 7, Folder 15-16)
  - Orders Granting Seller's License, 1903-1916 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Petitions, 1905-1918 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Sellers Bond, 1891-1916 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Miscellaneous, 1903-1916 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Orders and Resolutions of the Town Board, 1871, 1900-1939 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Schools
  - Census Statistics, 1895-1906 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - District Clerk's Report of Census Statistics, 1865-1906 (Box 8, Folder 6-7)
  - Joint District Census Statistics, 1898-1906 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Report to the County Superintendent, 1897-1906 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - School District Reorganization, 1862-1921 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Text Book Lists, 1925 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Tuition, 1917-1921, 1948-1949 (Box 8, Folder 12-15)
- State Department of Agriculture Bulletin, 1919 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Statistics of Outdoor Relief, 1883 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Taxation Records
  - 1863-1933 (Box 8, Folder 18-25)
  - 1934-1957 (Box 9, Folder 1-9)